{
    "subject": "resource/Ben_Chapman_(actor)",
    "predicate": "ontology/activeYearsStartYear",
    "object": "1949",
    "human_readable": "Ben Chapman started his acting career in 1949.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9540830254554749,
            "question": "When did Ben Chapman begin his acting career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7367830276489258,
            "question": "In what decade did Ben Chapman start acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7362605333328247,
            "question": "Where did Ben Chapman primarily work during his acting career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7251279354095459,
            "question": "Did Ben Chapman have a long and successful acting career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7064979672431946,
            "question": "What year marked the start of Ben Chapman's acting journey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47440105676651,
            "question": "Is Ben Chapman known for his work in film, television, or theatre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46496421098709106,
            "question": "What other notable actors worked with Ben Chapman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4252510666847229,
            "question": "Has Ben Chapman received any notable awards for his acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34077104926109314,
            "question": "What kind of roles is Ben Chapman best known for playing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14043444395065308,
            "question": "What are some of Ben Chapman's most popular movies or television shows?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ben Chapman started his acting career in 1949.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2143_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of roles is Ben Chapman best known for playing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2143_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Ben Chapman received any notable awards for his acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2143_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other notable actors worked with Ben Chapman?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2143_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2143_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2143_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2143_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2143_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2143_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2143_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2143_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2143_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2143_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2143_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nWhile the documents state that Ben Chapman's first film role was a bit in \"Pagan Love Song\" (1950), they don't mention a specific start date for his acting career. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Ben Chapman's first movie job was a bit part in MGM's \"Pagan Love Song\" (1950), which is later than the year mentioned in the query. Therefore, the statement that he started his acting career in 1949 is not supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Ben Chapman started his acting career in movies with the bit part in \"Pagan Love Song\" (1950), not in 1949.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It states he started his acting career in 1949, but text says he landed a bit part in the 1950 musical \"Pagan Love Song\", which implies his first film role was in 1950.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "there is no information provided to support the start of Ben Chapman's acting career being 1949, whereas, the text mentions that his first movie job was a bit in MGM's \"Pagan Love Song\" (1950) indicating that his acting career started in 1950.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information indicates that Ben Chapman did not start his acting career in 1949. According to the provided details, he worked as a Tahitian dancer in nightclubs which led to his first movie job, playing a bit part in MGM's \"Pagan Love Song\" in 1950. Additionally, his military service temporarily sidetracked what was described as a modest screen career before his well-known role as the Gill Man in 1954. Therefore, 1949 is not supported by the given context.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}